Office of the President Records UA001
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Jean Mayer, administrative records and related papers, 1939 -- 2006; 1976 -- 1992; UA001.013; 45.6 Linear Feet; 2 Digital Object(s)
  - Subject files, 1939 -- 1996; UA001.013.001
    - Admissions, 1977; UA001.013.001.00022 (Box 1)
    - Admissions, 1977; UA001.013.001.00023 (Box 1)
    - Admissions, 1978 -- 1979; UA001.013.001.00024 (Box 1)
    - Admissions, 1983 -- 1984; UA001.013.001.00025 (Box 1)
    - Admissions, 1986; UA001.013.001.00026 (Box 1)
    - Advisory Committee on Engineering, 1974; UA001.013.001.00027 (Box 1)
    - Advisory Committee on Faculty Personnel, 1971 -- 1978; UA001.013.001.00028 (Box 1)
    - Advisory Council on Minority and Women's Affairs, 1976 -- 1977; UA001.013.001.00029 (Box 1)
    - Advisory Committee on University Investment, 1978 -- 1979; UA001.013.001.00030 (Box 1)
    - Advisory Committee for School of Veterinary Medicine, 1977 -- 1978; UA001.013.001.00031 (Box 1)
    - Affiliation agreement with the Oceanic Institute, 1978; UA001.013.001.00032 (Box 1)
    - Affirmative action, 1976; UA001.013.001.00033 (Box 1)
    - Affirmative action, 1981 -- 1982; UA001.013.001.00034 (Box 1)
    - Affirmative action, 1982; UA001.013.001.00035 (Box 1)
    - Affirmative action, 1983 -- 1985; UA001.013.001.00036 (Box 1)
    - Affirmative action: general (confidential), 1980 -- 1981; UA001.013.001.00037 (Box 1)
    - Affirmative action: handicapped (BCH), 1973 -- 1974; UA001.013.001.00038 (Box 1)
    - Affirmative action: Committee on the Handicapped, 1977 -- 1980; UA001.013.001.00039 (Box 1)
    - Affirmative action: Committtee on Persons with Disabilities (AA), 1977 -- 1979; UA001.013.001.00040 (Box 1)
    - Affirmative action: Committee on Persons with Disabilities, 1980; UA001.013.001.00041 (Box 1)
    - Affirmative action: Presidential Review Council, 1980; UA001.013.001.00042 (Box 1)
    - Affirmative action: Title IX, 1977 -- 1981; UA001.013.001.00043 (Box 1)
    - Affirmative action: Title IX, 1975 -- 1976; UA001.013.001.00044 (Box 1)
    - African-American Center, 1980 -- 1981; UA001.013.002.00001 (Box 2)
    - African-American issues, 1984 -- 1991; UA001.013.002.00002 (Box 2)
    - Aid: Niger, 1984 -- 1996; UA001.013.002.00003 (Box 2)
    - Robert A. Albert, 1970 -- 1972; UA001.013.002.00004 (Box 2)
    - Alma mater, 1985 -- 1986; UA001.013.002.00005 (Box 2)
    - Alumni clubs, 1976 -- 1983; UA001.013.002.00006 (Box 2)
    - Alumni Council, 1977; UA001.013.002.00007 (Box 2)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1976 -- 1977; UA001.013.002.00008 (Box 2)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1981 -- 1982; UA001.013.002.00009 (Box 2)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1983 -- 1984; UA001.013.002.00010 (Box 2)
    - American Council on Education, 1977; UA001.013.002.00011 (Box 2)
    - American Council on Education: general, 1978; UA001.013.002.00012 (Box 2)
    - Anderson Hall renovation, 1985; UA001.013.002.00013 (Box 2)
    - Aquaculture (Oceanic Institute), 1980 -- 1982; UA001.013.002.00014 (Box 2)
    - Architecture program, 1983 -- 1984; UA001.013.002.00015 (Box 2)
    - Associations, 1983 -- 1985; UA001.013.002.00016 (Box 2)
    - Association of American Colleges, 1976 -- 1980; UA001.013.002.00017 (Box 2)
    - Association for Biomedical Research, 1980 -- 1982; UA001.013.002.00018 (Box 2)
    - Athletics, 1980 -- 1989; UA001.013.002.00019 (Box 2)
    - Burton C. Hallowell: general, 1975 -- 1977; UA001.013.002.00020 (Box 2)
    - Boston School of Occupational Therapy (BSOT) and Burton C. Hallowell, 1969 -- 1971; UA001.013.002.00021 (Box 2)
    - Boston School of Occupational Therapy (BSOT), 1973 -- 1981; UA001.013.002.00022 (Box 2)
    - Boston School of Occupational Therapy (BSOT), 1985 -- 1987; UA001.013.002.00023 (Box 2)
    - Boston School of Occupational Therapy (BSOT), 1989; UA001.013.002.00024 (Box 2)
    - Boston School of Occupational Therapy (BSOT): undergraduate phase-out letters, 1986; UA001.013.002.00025 (Box 2)
    - Ballou Medal, 1939 -- 1978; UA001.013.002.00026 (Box 2)
    - Ballou Hall sit-in, 1985; UA001.013.002.00027 (Box 2)
    - Curtis Barnes, 1979 -- 1985; UA001.013.002.00028 (Box 2)
    - Barnum fire, 1975 -- 1976; UA001.013.002.00029 (Box 2)
    - Bay State Skills Corporation, 1984 -- 1988; UA001.013.002.00030 (Box 2)
    - Benefits: maternity, 1988; UA001.013.002.00031 (Box 2)
    - Better World Society, 1990; UA001.013.002.00032 (Box 2)
    - Beech Nut Baby Foods, 1976 -- 1977; UA001.013.002.00033 (Box 2)
    - Henry Bellmon, 1978; UA001.013.002.00034 (Box 2)
    - Bicentennial of the French Revolution, 1989; UA001.013.002.00035 (Box 2)
    - Biology, 1991 -- 1992; UA001.013.002.00036 (Box 2)
    - Biology, 1983 -- 1984; UA001.013.002.00037 (Box 2)
    - Biochemistry and pharmacology, 1986 -- 1987; UA001.013.002.00038 (Box 2)
    - Biomedical Imaging Center, 1988; UA001.013.002.00039 (Box 2)
    - Board of Regents: higher education, 1982; UA001.013.002.00040 (Box 2)
    - Board of Overseers prior to 1990, 1985 -- 1989; UA001.013.002.00041 (Box 2)
    - Bomb leads, 1981; UA001.013.002.00042 (Box 2)
    - Boston, 1978 -- 1980; UA001.013.002.00043 (Box 2)
    - City of Boston, 1981 -- 1983; UA001.013.002.00044 (Box 2)
    - Desegregation of Boston public schools, 1981 -- 1982; UA001.013.002.00045 (Box 2)
    - Boston school desegregation (Burton C. Hallowell), 1975; UA001.013.002.00046 (Box 2)
    - Boston school desegregation (Burton C. Hallowell), 1975; UA001.013.002.00047 (Box 2)
    - Boston schools desegregation plan, 1975; UA001.013.003.00001 (Box 3)
    - Boston schools desegregation, 1976; UA001.013.003.00002 (Box 3)
    - Boston schools desegregation, 1977; UA001.013.003.00003 (Box 3)
    - Boston public schools and desegregation, 1983 -- 1987; UA001.013.003.00004 (Box 3)
    - Board of Regents (Massachusetts), 1986 -- 1988; UA001.013.003.00005 (Box 3)
    - Edward Brooke, 1978; UA001.013.003.00006 (Box 3)
    - George E. Brown and Congress, 1984; UA001.013.003.00007 (Box 3)
    - Budgets: Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy (FSLD), School of Engineering (ENG), Tufts University School of Medicine (TUSM), 1978 -- 1984; UA001.013.003.00008 (Box 3)
    - Budget, 1975 -- 1977; UA001.013.003.00009 (Box 3)
    - Budget, 1977 -- 1978; UA001.013.003.00010 (Box 3)
    - Budget, 1978 -- 1979; UA001.013.003.00011 (Box 3)
    - Budget, 1979 -- 1980; UA001.013.003.00012 (Box 3)
    - Budget, 1991 -- 1993; UA001.013.003.00013 (Box 3)
    - Budget Office, 1979 -- 1982; UA001.013.003.00014 (Box 3)
    - Bursar, 1985 -- 1990; UA001.013.003.00015 (Box 3)
    - John Bush/Bush Medals, 1982 -- 1985; UA001.013.003.00016 (Box 3)
    - CETA Program, 1979; UA001.013.003.00017 (Box 3)
    - CIA recruitment on campus, 1984 -- 1985; UA001.013.003.00018 (Box 3)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Education (CUE) (Burton C. Hallowell), 1971 -- 1976; UA001.013.003.00019 (Box 3)
    - Corporation Visiting Committees (CVC), 1984 -- 1987; UA001.013.003.00020 (Box 3)
    - Corporation Visiting Committee (CVC): admissions, 1970 -- 1976; UA001.013.003.00021 (Box 3)
    - Corporation Visiting Committee (CVC): arts, 1977 -- 1987; UA001.013.003.00022 (Box 3)
    - Corporation Visiting Committee (CVC): arts, 1981; UA001.013.003.00023 (Box 3)
    - Corporation Visiting Committee (CVC): arts, 1976; UA001.013.003.00024 (Box 3)
    - Corporation Visiting Committee (CVC): Boston School of Occupational Therapy (BSOT) (Burton C. Hallowell), 1968 -- 1970; UA001.013.003.00025 (Box 3)
    - Corporation Visiting Committee (CVC): chemistry (Burton C. Hallowell), 1969 -- 1971; UA001.013.003.00026 (Box 3)
    - Corporation Visiting Committee (CVC): Dental School, 1977 -- 1978; UA001.013.003.00027 (Box 3)
    - Corporation Visiting Committee (CVC): Tufts University School of Dental Medicine (Burton C. Hallowell), 1974 -- 1976; UA001.013.003.00028 (Box 3)
    - Corporaton Visiting Committee (CVC): Eliot- Pearson (Burton C. Hallowell), 1964 -- 1970; UA001.013.003.00029 (Box 3)
    - Corporation Visiting Committee (CVC): engineering, 1982; UA001.013.003.00030 (Box 3)
    - Corporation Visiting Committee (CVC): engineering, 1972 -- 1976; UA001.013.003.00031 (Box 3)
    - Corporation Visiting Committee (CVC): engineering, 1979 -- 1980; UA001.013.003.00032 (Box 3)
    - Corporation Visiting Committee (CVC): Fletcher School, 1979 -- 1983; UA001.013.003.00033 (Box 3)
    - Corporation Visiting Committee (CVC): Fletcher School, 1978 -- 1985; UA001.013.003.00034 (Box 3)
    - Corporation Visiting Committee (CVC): Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy, 1973 -- 1976; UA001.013.004.00001 (Box 4)
    - Corporation Visiting Committee (CVC): Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy (FSLD), 1976 -- 1977; UA001.013.004.00002 (Box 4)
    - Corporation Visiting Committee (CVC): general, 1973 -- 1976; UA001.013.004.00003 (Box 4)
    - Corporation Visiting Committee (CVC): general, 1977 -- 1978; UA001.013.004.00004 (Box 4)
    - Corporation Visiting Committee (CVC): library, 1977 -- 1982; UA001.013.004.00005 (Box 4)
    - Corporation Visiting Committee (CVC): library (Burton C. Hallowell), 1974 -- 1975; UA001.013.004.00006 (Box 4)
    - Corporation Visiting Committee (CVC): library, 1976; UA001.013.004.00007 (Box 4)
    - Corporation Visiting Committee (CVC): library, 1974 -- 1977; UA001.013.004.00008 (Box 4)
    - Corporation Visiting Committee (CVC): Medical School, 1981 -- 1987; UA001.013.004.00009 (Box 4)
    - Corporation Visiting Committee (CVC): Medical School, 1976 -- 1977; UA001.013.004.00010 (Box 4)
    - Corporation Visiting Committee (CVC): Nutrition, 1982 -- 1983; UA001.013.004.00011 (Box 4)
    - Corporation Visiting Committee (CVC): religious life and chaplaincy, 1976 -- 1977; UA001.013.004.00012 (Box 4)
    - Corporation Visiting Committee (CVC): religious life and chaplaincy, 1978; UA001.013.004.00013 (Box 4)
    - Corporation Visiting Committee (CVC): Veterinary School, 1980 -- 1981; UA001.013.004.00014 (Box 4)
    - Cable tv, 1978 -- 1980; UA001.013.004.00015 (Box 4)
    - Campus Center, 1983 -- 1986; UA001.013.004.00016 (Box 4)
    - Campus Center: Barnes and Noble, 1990 -- 1991; UA001.013.004.00017 (Box 4)
    - Capital Project: decision process, 1979 -- 1980; UA001.013.004.00018 (Box 4)
    - Carmichael, Leonard (Burton C. Hallowell), 1967 -- 1974; UA001.013.004.00019 (Box 4)
    - Carpenter House fire, 1979; UA001.013.004.00020 (Box 4)
    - Center for Environmental Management, 1992; UA001.013.004.00021 (Box 4)
    - Center for Environmental Management, 1983 -- 1984; UA001.013.004.00022 (Box 4)
    - Center for Environmental Management, 1983 -- 1984; UA001.013.004.00023 (Box 4)
    - Center for Environmental Management, 1983 -- 1989; UA001.013.004.00024 (Box 4)
    - Center for Environmental Management, 1990 -- 1991; UA001.013.004.00025 (Box 4)
    - Center for Environmental Management, 1992; UA001.013.004.00026 (Box 4)
    - Chaplaincy files, 1985 -- 1987; UA001.013.004.00027 (Box 4)
      75 years from date of creation.
    - Chaplaincy, 1987 -- 1988; UA001.013.004.00028 (Box 4)
    - Chaplaincy search, 1983 -- 1984; UA001.013.004.00029 (Box 4)
    - Chaplaincy, 1982 -- 1984; UA001.013.004.00030 (Box 4)
    - Chaplaincy, 1988 -- 1989; UA001.013.004.00031 (Box 4)
    - Chasdi, Shimon, 1978; UA001.013.004.00032 (Box 4)
    - Chemistry, 1985; UA001.013.004.00033 (Box 4)
    - Chemistry, 1983 -- 1985; UA001.013.004.00034 (Box 4)
    - Chemistry, 1986 -- 1987; UA001.013.004.00035 (Box 4)
    - Chemistry, 1987 -- 1992; UA001.013.005.00001 (Box 5)
    - Child Care Panel, 1982; UA001.013.005.00002 (Box 5)
    - Child Study, 1980 -- 1981; UA001.013.005.00003 (Box 5)
    - Child Study, 1987 -- 1991; UA001.013.005.00004 (Box 5)
    - Children's Literature Foundation, 1987 -- 1988; UA001.013.005.00005 (Box 5)
    - Child, Youth, and Family Policy Workshop, 1989 -- 1990; UA001.013.005.00006 (Box 5)
    - China (misc.), 1983 -- 1984; UA001.013.005.00007 (Box 5)
    - China (misc.), 1985; UA001.013.005.00008 (Box 5)
    - China (misc.), 1986; UA001.013.005.00009 (Box 5)
    - China: general, 1987 -- 1989; UA001.013.005.00010 (Box 5)
    - Chinese program, 1979 -- 1983; UA001.013.005.00011 (Box 5)
    - Classics, 1983 -- 1985; UA001.013.005.00012 (Box 5)
    - Classics, 1967 -- 1981; UA001.013.005.00013 (Box 5)
    - Classics, 1964 -- 1984; UA001.013.005.00014 (Box 5)
    - Classics, 1987 -- 1988; UA001.013.005.00015 (Box 5)
    - Classics, 1990 -- 1991; UA001.013.005.00016 (Box 5)
    - Clippings, 1975 -- 1978; UA001.013.005.00017 (Box 5)
    - Clippings, 1976 -- 1990; UA001.013.005.00018 (Box 5)
    - Commencement, 1976; UA001.013.005.00019 (Box 5)
    - Commencement, 1977; UA001.013.005.00020 (Box 5)
    - Commencement, 1978; UA001.013.005.00021 (Box 5)
    - Commencement, 1980; UA001.013.005.00022 (Box 5)
    - Commencement, 1987; UA001.013.005.00023 (Box 5)
    - Committee on Biological Sciences, 1977; UA001.013.005.00024 (Box 5)
    - Committee on the Future of Graduate Studies, 1979; UA001.013.005.00025 (Box 5)
    - Committee on Libraries, 1974 -- 1975; UA001.013.005.00026 (Box 5)
    - Committee on Public Health, 1977; UA001.013.005.00027 (Box 5)
    - Committee on Research Policies and Procedures, 1978; UA001.013.005.00028 (Box 5)
    - Committee on Student Life, 1976 -- 1982; UA001.013.005.00029 (Box 5)
    - Tenure and promotion, 1976 -- 1983; UA001.013.005.00030 (Box 5)
    - Committee on Visual Arts, 1968 -- 1981; UA001.013.005.00031 (Box 5)
    - Community affairs, 1978 -- 1983; UA001.013.005.00032 (Box 5)
    - Community affairs, 1977; UA001.013.005.00033 (Box 5)
    - Community Health Program, 1976; UA001.013.005.00034 (Box 5)
    - Community relations, 1984 -- 1986; UA001.013.005.00035 (Box 5)
    - Community relations (Somerville/Medford), 1981 -- 1983; UA001.013.005.00036 (Box 5)
    - Community relations, 1987; UA001.013.005.00037 (Box 5)
    - Community relations, 1988 -- 1992; UA001.013.005.00038 (Box 5)
    - Commonwealth of Massachusetts and Michael S. Dukakis, 1983 -- 1991; UA001.013.006.00001 (Box 6)
    - Computer Center, n.d., UA001.013.006.00002 (Box 6)
    - Computer Center, 1974; UA001.013.006.00003 (Box 6)
    - Computer science, 1985 -- 1991; UA001.013.006.00004 (Box 6)
    - Conference Bureau, 1976; UA001.013.006.00005 (Box 6)
    - Conference Bureau, 1977 -- 1978; UA001.013.006.00006 (Box 6)
    - Volpe Construction case, 1970 -- 1973; UA001.013.006.00007 (Box 6)
    - Volpe Construction case, 1969 -- 1974; UA001.013.006.00008 (Box 6)
    - Continuing education, 1981; UA001.013.006.00009 (Box 6)
    - Silvio Conte, 1984 -- 1987; UA001.013.006.00010 (Box 6)
    - Continuing education, 1976; UA001.013.006.00011 (Box 6)
    - Continuing education, 1977 -- 1980; UA001.013.006.00012 (Box 6)
    - Convocation, 1992; UA001.013.006.00013 (Box 6)
    - Coolidge room portraits, 1977; UA001.013.006.00014 (Box 6)
    - Copyrights, 1964; UA001.013.006.00015 (Box 6)
    - Counseling Center, 1977; UA001.013.006.00016 (Box 6)
    - Crackpots, 1978 -- 1982; UA001.013.006.00017 (Box 6)
    - Crane Theological School, 1967 -- 1968; UA001.013.006.00018 (Box 6)
    - Crane Theological School, 1968 -- 1977; UA001.013.006.00019 (Box 6)
    - Criterion, 1976; UA001.013.006.00020 (Box 6)
    - Council of Deans, 1980 -- 1982; UA001.013.006.00021 (Box 6)
    - Dana #2, 1982 -- 1986; UA001.013.006.00022 (Box 6)
    - Decision-making, 1983 -- 1985; UA001.013.006.00023 (Box 6)
    - Decision-Making Program, 1978 -- 1982; UA001.013.006.00024 (Box 6)
    - Decision-making, 1976; UA001.013.006.00025 (Box 6)
    - Dental Clinic, 1973 -- 1983; UA001.013.006.00026 (Box 6)
    - Dental School, 1976; UA001.013.006.00027 (Box 6)
    - Dental School, 1976; UA001.013.006.00028 (Box 6)
    - Dental School, 1977; UA001.013.006.00029 (Box 6)
    - Dental School: general, 1977 -- 1982; UA001.013.006.00030 (Box 6)
    - Dental School, 1988 -- 1990; UA001.013.006.00031 (Box 6)
    - Dental School, 1990; UA001.013.006.00032 (Box 6)
    - Dental School: accreditation, 1963; UA001.013.006.00033 (Box 6)
    - Dental School: accreditation, 1970 -- 1971; UA001.013.006.00034 (Box 6)
    - Dental School: accreditation, 1973; UA001.013.006.00035 (Box 6)
    - Dental School: accreditation, 1977; UA001.013.006.00036 (Box 6)
    - Dental School: admissions, 1972 -- 1981; UA001.013.006.00037 (Box 6)
    - Dental School: admissions, 1985 -- 1987; UA001.013.006.00038 (Box 6)
    - Dental School: budget, 1977 -- 1980; UA001.013.007.00001 (Box 7)
    - Dental School: bylaws, 1959 -- 1984; UA001.013.007.00002 (Box 7)
    - Dental School: general, 1984 -- 1986; UA001.013.007.00003 (Box 7)
    - Dental School: commencement, 1979 -- 1988; UA001.013.007.00004 (Box 7)
    - Dental School: Dean Johansen, 1978 -- 1983; UA001.013.007.00005 (Box 7)
    - Dental School: Maine Program, 1966 -- 1972; UA001.013.007.00006 (Box 7)
    - Dental School: ex-faculty and general faculty, 1980; UA001.013.007.00007 (Box 7)
    - Dental School: workshop and preceptorship training, 1976 -- 1977; UA001.013.007.00008 (Box 7)
    - Deptartment of Art and History of Architecture, 1985 -- 1991; UA001.013.007.00009 (Box 7)
    - Divestment: South Africa, 1978 -- 1981; UA001.013.007.00010 (Box 7)
    - Divestment: South Africa, 1985; UA001.013.007.00011 (Box 7)
    - Dole, Robert, 1984 -- 1986; UA001.013.007.00012 (Box 7)
    - Donations: requests, 1987 -- 1988; UA001.013.007.00013 (Box 7)
    - Draft registration, 1983; UA001.013.007.00014 (Box 7)
    - Dragan Foundation, 1986 -- 1990; UA001.013.007.00015 (Box 7)
    - Drama Center, 1984 -- 1985; UA001.013.007.00016 (Box 7)
    - Drama and dance, 1986 -- 1992; UA001.013.007.00017 (Box 7)
    - Drama Center, 1979 -- 1983; UA001.013.007.00018 (Box 7)
    - Peter Dreier case, 1983; UA001.013.007.00019 (Box 7)
    - Department of Urban and Environmental Policy (DUEP), 1984 -- 1988; UA001.013.007.00020 (Box 7)
    - Memos of Jack Dunn, 1972 -- 1979; UA001.013.007.00021 (Box 7)
    - Memos of Jack Dunn, 1984 -- 1990; UA001.013.007.00022 (Box 7)
    - Thomas Eagleton, 1977 -- 1979; UA001.013.007.00023 (Box 7)
    - Economics, 1986 -- 1989; UA001.013.007.00024 (Box 7)
    - Education, 1976 -- 1984; UA001.013.007.00025 (Box 7)
    - Department of Education, 1983 -- 1989; UA001.013.007.00026 (Box 7)
    - Department of Education, 1962 -- 1983; UA001.013.007.00027 (Box 7)
    - Education, 1989 -- 1992; UA001.013.007.00028 (Box 7)
    - Education: Tufts vs. Carton, 1972 -- 1981; UA001.013.007.00029 (Box 7)
    - Educational Policy Committee (EPC), 1975 -- 1981; UA001.013.007.00030 (Box 7)
    - Dean Theodore Eliott, 1978 -- 1981; UA001.013.007.00031 (Box 7)
    - Endowed chairs, 1971 -- 1975; UA001.013.007.00032 (Box 7)
    - Energy, 1974 -- 1977; UA001.013.007.00033 (Box 7)
    - Engineering, 1984 -- 1988; UA001.013.007.00034 (Box 7)
    - Engineering, 1983 -- 1985; UA001.013.007.00035 (Box 7)
    - Engineering, 1985 -- 1986; UA001.013.007.00036 (Box 7)
    - Engineering, 1976 -- 1979; UA001.013.007.00037 (Box 7)
    - Engineering, 1979 -- 1983; UA001.013.008.00001 (Box 8)
    - Engineering, 1980 -- 1992; UA001.013.008.00002 (Box 8)
    - Engineering accreditation, 1964 -- 1972; UA001.013.008.00003 (Box 8)
    - Engineering School: ECPD, 1939 -- 1964; UA001.013.008.00004 (Box 8)
    - Engineering School: ECPD accreditation, 1975 -- 1982; UA001.013.008.00005 (Box 8)
    - Engineering School: 100th anniversary, 1972 -- 1973; UA001.013.008.00006 (Box 8)
    - English, 1988; UA001.013.008.00007 (Box 8)
    - English, 1987 -- 1992; UA001.013.008.00008 (Box 8)
    - Enrollment, 1973 -- 1980; UA001.013.008.00009 (Box 8)
    - Environmental decision-making, 1990 -- 1992; UA001.013.008.00010 (Box 8)
    - Environmental management, 1983; UA001.013.008.00011 (Box 8)
    - Executive vice-president, 1979 -- 1981; UA001.013.008.00012 (Box 8)
    - Ex-College, 1977 -- 1982; UA001.013.008.00013 (Box 8)
    - Ex-College: "Zionism Reconsidered", 1973 -- 1974; UA001.013.008.00014 (Box 8)
    - Ex-College: symposium project (later to be named Education for Public Inquiry and International Citizenship [EPIIC]), 1988 -- 1989; UA001.013.008.00015 (Box 8)
    - Tufts European Center in Talloires, France, 1983 -- 1986; UA001.013.008.00016 (Box 8)
    - "Eyes on the Prize" archive, 1987 -- 1990; UA001.013.008.00017 (Box 8)
    - Facilities planning, 1976 -- 1979; UA001.013.008.00018 (Box 8)
    - Faculty: general, 1979 -- 1983; UA001.013.008.00019 (Box 8)
    - Faculty of Arts, 1985 -- 1988; UA001.013.008.00020 (Box 8)
    - Faculty Club, 1976 -- 1977; UA001.013.008.00021 (Box 8)
    - Faculty committees, 1978; UA001.013.008.00022 (Box 8)
    - Faculty Committee on Environment, Health, and Safety, 1969 -- 1976; UA001.013.008.00023 (Box 8)
    - Committee on Tenure and Promotion, 1970 -- 1974; UA001.013.008.00024 (Box 8)
    - Faculty grievances procedure, 1977 -- 1981; UA001.013.008.00025 (Box 8)
    - Faculty salaries and tenure, 1973 -- 1976; UA001.013.008.00026 (Box 8)
    - Faculty: salaries, tenure and academic freedom, 1968 -- 1970; UA001.013.008.00027 (Box 8)
    - Faculty: salaries, tenure and academic freedom, 1971 -- 1972; UA001.013.008.00028 (Box 8)
    - Faculty workload, 1975; UA001.013.008.00029 (Box 8)
    - Faculty: liberal arts and Jackson College, 1987; UA001.013.008.00030 (Box 8)
    - Famine, 1986 -- 1988; UA001.013.008.00031 (Box 8)
    - Famine in the Sudan, 1985 -- 1988; UA001.013.008.00032 (Box 8)
    - Famine Center: part I, 1985; UA001.013.008.00033 (Box 8)
    - Famine Center: part II, 1986 -- 1988; UA001.013.009.00001 (Box 9)
    - Famine Center: part III, 1987 -- 1988; UA001.013.009.00002 (Box 9)
    - Feasibility study: Tufts University School of Medicine (TUSM) and the College of Arts & Sciences, 1977; UA001.013.009.00003 (Box 9)
    - Federal grantsmanship, 1981 -- 1984; UA001.013.009.00004 (Box 9)
    - Fellowships and grants, 1977 -- 1980; UA001.013.009.00005 (Box 9)
    - Fellowships, 1983 -- 1990; UA001.013.009.00006 (Box 9)
    - Mason Fernald, 1977 -- 1978; UA001.013.009.00007 (Box 9)
    - Memos of Mason Fernald, 1979 -- 1980; UA001.013.009.00008 (Box 9)
    - Memos of Mason Fernald, 1981 -- 1982; UA001.013.009.00009 (Box 9)
    - Fernberg, Sylvia G., 1984 -- 1987; UA001.013.009.00010 (Box 9)
    - Finances, 1981 -- 1983; UA001.013.009.00011 (Box 9)
    - Finances, 1976 -- 1977; UA001.013.009.00012 (Box 9)
    - Finances, 1979 -- 1980; UA001.013.009.00013 (Box 9)
    - Fine arts, 1981 -- 1988; UA001.013.009.00014 (Box 9)
    - Fine arts, 1978 -- 1983; UA001.013.009.00015 (Box 9)
    - Fine arts, 1969 -- 1985; UA001.013.009.00016 (Box 9)
    - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy (FSLD): general, 1979 -- 1981; UA001.013.009.00017 (Box 9)
    - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy (FSLD), 1974; UA001.013.009.00018 (Box 9)
    - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy (FSLD), 1976; UA001.013.009.00019 (Box 9)
    - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy (FSLD), 1977; UA001.013.009.00020 (Box 9)
    - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy (FSLD), 1978; UA001.013.009.00021 (Box 9)
    - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy (FSLD) and the Institute for Foreign Policy Analysis (IFPA), 1983 -- 1988; UA001.013.009.00022 (Box 9)
    - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy (FSLD), 1989 -- 1991; UA001.013.009.00023 (Box 9)
    - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy (FSLD), 1984 -- 1988; UA001.013.009.00024 (Box 9)
    - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy (FSLD) and the Asia Pacific Teaching Program, 1976 -- 1978; UA001.013.009.00025 (Box 9)
    - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy (FSLD) and BIFAD, 1977; UA001.013.009.00026 (Box 9)
    - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy (FSLD): by-laws, UA001.013.009.00027 (Box 9)
    - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy (FSLD): Capital Project, 1976; UA001.013.009.00028 (Box 9)
    - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy (FSLD): Clayton Lectures, 1966 -- 1975; UA001.013.009.00029 (Box 9)